Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence (Box-folder 90/2, Box-folder 102/10-14)
  Correspondence series is represented by four letters and one telegram.
  Arrangement is by date.
  - TLS from Harry N. Wessel to Jerome Kern, dated 5/10/13; [1] p. (Box-folder 102/10)
  - ALS from Charles Previn to Mr. Dreyfus, n.d.; [1] p. Note: written "at request of Mr. Erlanger" (Box-folder 102/11)
  - ALS from Kern to John [?], ca. 2/18/28. Note: subject of note is script for Oh, Lady! Lady!! (Box-folder 102/12)
  - ALS from Kern to [P.G.] Wodehouse, date 6/15/28. Note: reply written on back of telegram from Wodehouse, the coded message is transcribed by Kern, his reply reads: "Wodehouse/17 Norfolk, Park Lane London./Attitude perfectly friendly but Laddie Cliff may fry himself before he can disassociate any portion libretto Oh Lady Lady from music/Love to Ethel. How is Snork./Jerry." (Box-folder 102/13)
  - Telegram from Mr. Dreyfus of Harms, Inc. to Eastman Symphony, London, dated 6/11/28. Note: subject is Kern's refusal to permit production of Oh, Lady! Lady!! with new music (Box-folder 102/14)
  - TLS from Genevieve Fisch of Benton & Bowles, Inc. advertising agency to Mr. Edgar Carver of Rodgers & Hammerstein re radio broadcast of Very Warm for May in 1951; [1] p. (Box-folder 90/2)